mcp/docker|MCP smart gateway used by the AI Tool Catalog
mcp/slack|Interact with Slack Workspaces over the Slack API.
mcp/grafana|MCP server for Grafana
mcp/aws-core-mcp-server|Starting point for using the awslabs MCP servers.
mcp/playwright|Playwright MCP server
mcp/fetch|Fetches a URL from the internet and extracts its contents as markdown
mcp/time|Time and timezone conversion capabilities
mcp/signatures|Repository containing cosign signatures for images in the mcp namespace
mcp/github-mcp-server|Official GitHub MCP Server, by GitHub. Provides seamless integration with GitHub APIs, enabling a...
mcp/sequentialthinking|Dynamic and reflective problem-solving through thought sequences.
mcp/context7|Context7 MCP Server -- Up-to-date code documentation for LLMs and AI code editors
mcp/wikipedia-mcp|A Model Context Protocol (MCP) server that retrieves information from Wikipedia to provide contex...
mcp/notion|Official Notion MCP Server
mcp/gitlab|MCP Server for the GitLab API, enabling project management, file operations, and more.
mcp/memory|Knowledge graph-based persistent memory system.
mcp/filesystem|Local filesystem access with configurable allowed paths
mcp/postgres|Connect with read-only access to PostgreSQL databases. This server enables LLMs to inspect databa...
mcp/duckduckgo|A Model Context Protocol (MCP) server that provides web search capabilities through DuckDuckGo, w...
mcp/brave-search|Search the Web for pages, images, news, videos, and more using the Brave Search API.
mcp/desktop-commander|Search, update, manage files and run terminal commands with AI
mcp/databutton|Databutton MCP Server
mcp/clickhouse|Official ClickHouse MCP Server
mcp/puppeteer|Browser automation and web scraping using Puppeteer.
mcp/github|Tools for interacting with the GitHub API, enabling file operations, repository management, searc...
mcp/azure|The Azure MCP Server, bringing the power of Azure to your agents.
